There's a slight concern weighing on my mind.
（ヴィルヘルム･
ヴァン･アストレア）
少しばかり 気がかりが生じました
I would like to take a small number
from our forces to eliminate it.
何名か連れて その排除に
向かいたく存じます
Is there any way I can help?
（エミリア）
私は 必要ありませんか？
Emilia-sama, head to safety in the carriage.
エミリア様は
このまま竜車で避難を
Do not release the children's hands.
どうぞ 子らの手を離さぬよう
You truly are master and servant.
やはり 主従なのでしょうな
あなた様の目は 彼とそっくりです
Your eyes look just like his.
Wilhelm-san, I—
ヴィルヘルムさん 私…
（ペテルギウス･ロマネコンティ）
あってはならないことなのデス！
This cannot be!
You cannot use such means, such tricks,
そのような手立てで 小細工で
私を 忠誠を ないがしろにー！
to make light of me and of my devotion!
This is some crappy game where,
once you're caught, it's over.
（ナツキ･スバル）
１回捕まったら
それで終わりのクソゲーだ
We must be crazy to entrust our lives to it,
それに命を預けるとか
どうかしてやがるぞ 俺も お前も！
you and me both!
My body is slowly getting used to this.
（ユリウス･ユークリウス）
少しずつ 体が慣れてきた
速度を上げるが？
Shall we speed up?
Go for it! Don't worry, I'll keep up!
（スバル）
ああ ついてくから安心してろ！
Wow.
スッゲー
Impossible.
バカな バカなバカなバカなバカな
Impossible, impossible, impossible, impossible.
Impossible!
バカな！
Why? How can it be?
なぜデス！ なぜなのデス！
I thought I was loved! I am loved!
私は愛されたはず！
愛されているはず！
By the witch, the witch, the witch, the witch!
魔女に！ 魔女に魔女に魔女に
The witch!
魔女にー！
It's time I finished you once and for all!
そろそろ 本気で
貴様を切らせてもらおう！
Al Clauseria!
アルクラウゼリア！
I will not let you do that.
そうはさせないのデス！
Ul Dona!
ウルドーナ
Burn, fighting spirit! Howl, magic ball!
（スバル）
燃えろ闘魂 うなれ魔球！
俺の本気は120キロちょいだぜっ！
When I get serious, I can pitch over 120 km/h!
What is this?
何デス…
You lost because you belittled him as powerless.
貴様の敗因は
彼を無力と侮ったことだ
My blade, of all six elements together,
will slice your very soul apart.
６属性を束ねた刃(やいば)は
貴様の魂すら 切り刻む
Scatter to the rainbow's end.
虹の彼方へ散るがいい
I will not let it end!
終われない　私は勤勉に
努めてきたのデス
I have been nothing but diligent.
The witch's love bathes my entire body!
魔女の寵(ちょう)愛を一身に浴びてー！
Julius, undo Nect!
ユリウス ネクトを解除しろ！
Very well.
承知した
Ah... My brain...
（スバル）ああ 脳が―
is trembling!
震える…
Yeah, just tremble while you wait.
おお… 震えて待ってろ
I'll play along with you, just this once...
特別に お前に会わせてやる
What are you saying? Who are you talking to?
何を？ 誰と？ 何の話を？
お待ちかねの魔女様にだ…
To the witch that you've been waiting for!
俺は 死に戻りをして…
I can Return by Death to—
あー！ やっと…
At last.
I've waited so long.
待ちわびたのデス
For your love, your merciful love,
your affectionate love...
あなたの愛を 慈愛を 寵愛を
No.
（魔女）違う
You are not the one.
あなたじゃない
I'm back!
戻ってきたー
This... cannot... be...
（ペテルギウス）
こんな… はずが… ないのデス
I was prepared to keep trying until you left me,
（スバル）
最悪 出てくまで何度でも
挑んでやるつもりだったってのに
but you gave up after one go?
How cowardly can you be?
１回でギブとは 根性無しも
いいとこだぜ てめえ
This time, I will guide you to your end.
今度こそ 終わりにしよう
Why...
なぜ… なぜ なぜ なぜ！
Why, why, why?
After everything I've done for you!
あれほどまでに あなたのために
尽くしたというのに！
Witch! Witch!
魔女よ！ 魔女よー！
Give me your love...
私に 寵愛を…
（スバル）ハア…
Petelgeuse Romanée-Conti...
ペテルギウス･ロマネコンティ
You were Sloth, all right.
お前 怠惰だったな
Subaru, let us hurry back to the village.
（ユリウス）
スバル すぐ村に戻ろう
Ferris just contacted me.
フェリスからの連絡だ
問題が発生したようだ
It seems there is a problem.
The fire stones that were in
the merchants' inventory are gone.
（フェリックス）
行商人たちの積み荷の目録にあった
火の魔石が ないらしいの
We unloaded all our cargo so we
could transport the villagers,
（オットー･スーウェン）
積み荷は全部降ろして―
代わりに 避難の村人たちを
乗せたはずなのに―
but the fire stones alone are missing.
火の魔石だけが
見当たらないんです
What does that mean?
どういう意味だ？
Someone left the stones on board
when they loaded the villagers.
（フェリックス）
何者かが 魔石を残したまま
村人たちを乗せたってこと
They were on Ketty-san's carriage.
（オットー）
ケティさんの竜車です
There are enough magic stones
to easily blow away a small village.
小さな集落くらい 軽々
消し飛ぶ量の魔石ですよ
Ketty's carriage is taking Emilia-sama
and the children to the capital.
ケティの竜車は エミリア様たち
王都避難組に利用されてる
（青年団長）エミリア様
Emilia-sama...
It's time.
そろそろ時間です
What's wrong?
（ダイン）どうしたの？
Are you okay?
（ミルド）大丈夫？
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい 何でもないの
It's nothing.
Come on, let's hurry!
さあ 急ぎましょう
Damn it!
（スバル）
クッソー！ 使えるもんは
何でも使う貧乏性が裏目に出た
My poor man's tendency to use
anything at hand backfired!
We have verified that no spell
was used to set a trap,
術式によるワナが
無いことは 確認した
but if something were physically
rigged in the carriage...
だが 竜車自体に 物理的な
仕掛けが施されているとしたら…
Ferris, could a land dragon catch up to them?
フェリス 今から地竜を飛ばして
追いつけるか？
Once they leave the Mathers domain
and get on the Lifaus Highway,
メイザース領を抜けて
リーファウス街道に入ってたら―
it'll be hard to catch them.
追いつくのは 厳しいかも
That still wasn't enough?
まだ足りないのか
これだけやって 俺は まだ…
Even after all that, I still can't...
May I say something?
（オットー）
１つ いいですか？
To tell you the truth, I'm in a pretty
desperate position right now.
（オットー）
僕は現状 かなり崖っぷちなんです
If you would accept a trade,
取り引きに応じて
くださるのであれば―
I promise to catch up to the carriage that lef—
先に出た竜車に
追いつくと お約束…
If there's anything I can do, I'll do it!
俺にできることなら
何だってやってやる！
Decisiveness is a good trait to have, Natsuki-san!
決断が早い人
嫌いじゃないですよ ナツキさん
I'll send Ia with you.
（ユリウス）
イアを君に同行させよう
本当なら 私も同行したいのだが…
I wish I could accompany you myself, but...
You're staying back, Julius.
ユリウスはダメ！
こんな傷だらけで
How do you expect to help them
with all those injuries?
何の役に立つの？
Nyot to mention your mana hasn't
even fully regenerated yet.
それに マナも
からっけつじゃにゃい
You just get some rest.
お前は安静にしてろ
全部片づけたら 祝賀会だ
Once this is over, we'll celebrate!
I'll make sure to invite you, so don't die.
招待客には入れてやるから
死ぬなよ！
Don't you die, either!
そっちこそ 死なないでね
Luck be with you.
武運を
Rather than take this road,
（オットー）
街道をまっすぐ… より
左の林に突っ込んだほうが早い
it's faster to go through the glade to the left.
It's the shortest way!
そっちが最短です
Man, your "soul of language"
divine protection is amazing.
（スバル）
にしても 言霊の加護ってすげえな
I had a hard time learning to control it.
（オットー）
うまく制御ができるまでは
大変だったんですよ
Since I can hear all creatures' voices,
from land dragons to insects.
なんせ 地竜から虫まで―
全ての生き物の声が
聞こえるんですから
But if we choose our path
based on what they say,
けど今は そいつらの
声を聞いて道を選べば―
this shortcut will work, and catching up
to Emilia and the kids will be easy!
森をショートカットできる
エミリアたちに
追いつくのも 簡単だ
What are you talking about?
（オットー）
何 言ってるやらですが
簡単ではないですから
It won't be easy at all!
We're gonna die!
死ぬーっ！
At this rate, we're seriously gonna die.
これ 間違いなく
そろそろ死ぬ 次は無い
This is it for us!
What is this? I feel a wind hitting me.
何でしょう 今 すごい風が来てる
Honestly, even I had no idea
I was capable of this—
正直 僕もここまでのことが
できるとは思ってませ…
What is it? What's wrong?
どうした 何があった
The trees are so loud.
木々が 騒がしいというか…
The birds and bugs began to make
a lot of noise, and then just vanished.
鳥や虫が大騒ぎして
急にいなくなりました
Something...
何か… 何かが来ます
Something is coming!
飛ばせ オットー
絶対に捕まるなよ！
Faster, Otto!
Don't get caught, no matter what!
Natsuki-san?
ナツキさん？
Just how persistent are you, damn it!?
てめえ…
どんだけしつこいんだよ
クソ野郎！
My body!
体をー！
My flesh body!
私の肉の体をー！
It's okay. Hang on tight.
大丈夫 しっかりつかまっていて
何も怖がる必要なんてないから
There's nothing to fear.
That old man just ran into someone behind us.
（パック）
後ろのほうで
あの お爺(じい)さんたちと
誰かが ぶつかったね
戦いになってる
They're fighting.
Do you know how many?
（エミリア）
相手の数は分かる？
A lot.
（パック）結構たくさん
But the old man's strength is nothing to mess with.
でも あのお爺さんが
冗談じゃなく すご腕だから―
Seems you and I won't be needed this time.
リアや 僕の出番はなさそうかな
Taking physical form without reason drains mana,
無意味に実体化してると
マナを食うし―
and I wouldn't want to
end up these kids' plaything.
子供たちのおもちゃに
されるのもね
If we could use your cuteness
to distract them from their fear,
（エミリア）
みんなの不安が パックの
かわいさでごまかせるなら
I think that'd be good in its own way, though.
それもいいかもって思うけど？
You say some scary things, my daughter.
（パック）
怖いこと言いだすなあ 僕の娘
Don't worry.
心配しないで
Whatever happens, I'll protect you.
何があっても お姉ちゃんが
みんなを守ってあげるから
W-We're fine!
だ… 大丈夫！
You don't have to worry about us!
お姉ちゃんのほうこそ
心配しないで！
（リュカ）
や… 約束したから
へっちゃらだし！
W-We made a promise, so this is nothing!
A promise?
約束って？
That we wouldn't let you go!
お姉ちゃんを離さないって約束！
Because if we aren't with you,
you'll do something crazy!
一緒にいてあげないと
ムチャするからって
And he'll worry if someone doesn't watch you!
誰か見ててあげないと
心配なんだって
Worry about me? Who told you this?
私を心配だって 誰に言われたの？
（ペトラ）
あっ ダメ それは…
Don't! We can't tell—
Subaru!
スバル！
Subaru said it.
スバルが言ってた
He said you get lonely easily, so he was worried!
寂しがり屋のお姉ちゃんが
心配だって
Subaru said...
スバルが… あっ…
Wait, we weren't supposed to tell her.
これって 言っちゃ
ダメだったんじゃ…
Oh, boy...
あちゃー…
Natsuki-san, is something coming up behind us?
（オットー）
ナツキさん 後ろに
何か来てるんですか？
Just some big, black animal.
（スバル）
ちょっとでかくて 黒いケダモノが
追っかけてきてるだけだ！
It has a wild voice and a scary face,
so you're better off not looking.
すんごい鳴き声で 顔も怖いから
見ないほうが吉！
Those things make me all the more curious!
露骨に気になる要素が
満載なんですが
Forget it! Just drive!
いいから飛ばせ！
If it chews through me,
you're gonna be its next meal.
俺が噛(か)まれたら
今度は お前もかじられるぞ！
Yikes!
ウヒー！
How many times do I have to play the last level?
何回 最終局面やらせんだ
What about you is slothful now,
you uselessly hard worker?
お前のどこが怠惰だ
この無用な働き者が！
Witch! Satella! Give me...
魔女ー！ サテラー！ また私をー！
Love! Love!
愛愛愛愛…
She doesn't love you or me...
（スバル）
俺も お前も愛されてなんかねえよ
Love! Love! Love! Love! Love!
In what kind of rom-com does someone
try to squash their love's heart?
好きな相手の心臓潰そうとする
ラブコメがあってたまるか！
Satella! Satella! Satella!
サテラ！ サテラサテラー！
I am your opponent.
お前の相手は俺だ
俺より前にいかせねえし―
I won't let you past me.
And I won't let you set foot near the person
up ahead. You can count on that.
俺の先にいる子に
追いつかせるわけにも―
絶対にいかねえ
Natsuki-san, you care about me that much?
ナツキさん そんなに僕のことを…
Will you be quiet?
ちょっと黙っててくれる？
今 かっこつけてるところだから
I'm trying to make myself look good.
Take this!
この！
Natsuki-san, we're leaving the forest!
ナツキさん 森を抜けます
Love...
（ペテルギウス）
愛 愛に愛す 愛だけが
全てなのデスー！
Love... Love me.
Love alone is everything!
（スバル）
エミリアんとこに お前を
連れてくわけにはいかねえんだよ！
I can't take you with me to where Emilia is!
I'm gonna need your strength,
力 借りるぜ
ユリウス･ユークリウス
Julius Juukulius!
Rental Goa!
レンタルゴーア！
Damn, that hurts...
だっ クソ痛(いて)え…
Give it to me.
（ペテルギウス）よこせ… 渡せ…
Hand it over.
I told you...
Relinquish it!
（スバル）
だから 俺の体に入っても―
If you try to enter my body,
you're just gonna get hurt!
痛い目に遭うだけだって
言ってんだろ！
The witch...
（ペテルギウス）
魔女に… サテラ サテラー！
Satella...
Satella!
I haven't forgotten a single moment
of the things you did for me!
あなたが私に ああ
片ときも忘れていないのデス！
あなたが忘れても 私は私は！
Even if you've forgotten,
I'll... I'll...
With all of my diligence,
私の勤勉さをもって
怠惰なる私と決別…
I'll part with my slothful self,
to repay your love...
If you had stayed a monster...
（スバル）
お前がバケモノのままだったら
俺の負けだったろうぜ
You might have beaten me!
（ペテルギウス）あ… サテラ
Satella...
（ペテルギウス）
終わ… 終わり
終わら… 終わらない
I... will not... I won't... let it end.
This hasn't ended...
終わってない
It hasn't.
クソーッ…
No, it's over.
（スバル）
いいや ここまでだ
ここで お前は―
As of now, you are
"finished"!
終 わ り だ！
Natsuki Subaru!
ナツキ･スバルー！
ハア…
This time, stay asleep forever, Petelgeuse.
今度こそ もうずっと眠ってろ
ペテルギウス
（オットー）
ナツキさん あれ！
Natsuki-san, look!
（スバル）
ヴィルヘルムさーん！
Wilhelm-san!
Subaru-dono!
（ヴィルヘルム）スバル殿！
Where's Emilia?
エミリアは？
Just ahead.
この先へ！ まっすぐに
大樹の方角です
Go straight, toward the great tree.
This is the perfect chance to repay my debt.
恩人に恩を返す 絶好の機会
Who can stand in the way of a man
on his way to see a woman?
男が女に会いに行くのを
誰にジャマされてなるものか
Natsuki-san, I see them!
ナツキさん 見えました！
避難の竜車 あれでしょう
That's the carriages with the refugees!
Back then,
（スバル）
あの時 誓ったんだ
I swore to myself.
No matter what it takes...
俺が 必ず―
I will save you.
お前を救ってみせる
（パック）
スバルのことを考えてる？
Are you thinking about Subaru?
Yeah.
（エミリア）
うん　でも…
やっぱり信じられない
But I still can't believe it.
If Subaru's really leading these forces,
（パック）
討伐隊を率いてたのが
スバルだったなら
lots of things would make sense.
いろいろ 納得がいくよ
Like why Ram didn't argue,
ラムが反発しなったのも
村人たちが避難に協力的だったのも
and why the villagers agreed to evacuate.
But why?
（エミリア）でも どうして？
After all the pain and suffering he went through...
あんなに傷つけて
あんなに苦しめて―
あんなに 悲しい顔までさせたのに
After I made him look so sad...
Why would he...
どうして 私を…
Lia, something is coming up behind us.
（パック）
リア 後ろから何か来る
Found them!
見つけた
むむむ… 思わぬ再会と思いきや
そういうことか
I thought this reunion was sudden.
So that's why you're here.
Wait! Why?
待って どうして…
Why?
どうして？
I love you, Emilia.
好きだよ エミリア
Damn it!
（スバル）
クソー 間に合えー！
Make it in time!
Thank you, Subaru.
ありがとう スバル
私を助けてくれて
Thank you for saving me.
（スバル）どこだ ここ…
Where am I?
I can't see a thing.
何も見えねえ 聞こえねえ
I can't hear a thing.
Is that witch lady coming to grab my heart again?
また 魔女の奴が
心臓つかみにやって来んのか…
I don't feel too bad, though.
けど 気分は悪くねえ
Subaru!
（エミリア）
スバル！ スバル！
Subaru!
Oh, hey.
（スバル）
ああ 何だ 聞こえたじゃねえか
I can hear, after all.
Subaru!
（エミリア）スバル！
Subaru, you're awake?
スバル 起きたのね
よかった ホントに
Thank goodness...
I'm so glad.
I'm lying down,
俺は寝っ転がってて
エミリアたんは 正座中
and Emilia-tan is kneeling.
And considering our distance
and the heavenly sensation under my head...
で この距離で 頭の下に―
天国のような感触があることを
念頭に入れると…
You don't have to go through that silly checklist.
そんな変な確認しなくても
ひざ枕よ
Your head is on my lap.
It isn't uncomfortable, is it?
寝心地 悪くない？
I know of no finer, more divine pillow.
これよりぜいたくで極楽な枕を
俺は知らないね
Um...
えーと…
Can I ask how things turned out?
いろいろと どうなったか
聞いてもいい？
もう
Honestly...
I'm the one who wants to ask what's going on.
いろいろと どうなってるのか
聞きたいのは 私のほうなのに
Is Patrasche okay?
（スバル）
パトラッシュは大丈夫？
I wanna become the wind
with my little friend again.
俺 今後もあいつと
風になりたいんだけど
She was burned pretty badly,
（エミリア）
ヤケドがひどかったけど
命に別状はないみたい
but her life's not in danger.
フェリスが見ててくれてる
Ferris is looking at her.
Oh, Ferris met up with us?
（スバル）
フェリスも合流してんだ
I have to ask, have I been out for a long while?
ひょっとして 俺
かなり長いこと寝てた？
About an hour or two.
（エミリア）
１ ２時間 ぐらいかな
Then, everyone's together now?
（スバル）
じゃあ みんな集まってるわけか
Julius, as well.
ユリウスも… ね
私 すごーく驚いちゃった
I was really surprised.
I never expected to see you two together.
スバルとユリウスが
一緒にいるなんて―
想像もしてなくて…
It was for reasons bluer than the mountains,
and taller than the seas, Emilia-tan.
そこは山より青く 海よりも
たかだかとした理由があんだよ
エミリアたん
俺 やっと戻ってきたんだな
I finally made it back.
I feel like I was having a really long dream.
長いこと 夢でも見てた気分だ
A terrible dream...
悪い夢を
No, it wasn't.
いや 違うな
A good dream, then?
いい夢 だった？
A good reality.
いいリアルだった
Back then, you asked me why...
あの日 君は俺に
どうしてって聞いたよな
Why I saved you...
どうして助けてくれるのか
Why I try so hard at everything...
どうして そんなに
いろいろ頑張るのか
You asked me why.
どうしてなのかって
Yeah.
（エミリア）
うん　そしたらスバルは
私がスバルを助けたからって
And you said it was because I saved you...
But I haven't done anything like that.
でも 私はそんなこと
してあげてない
I've never been able to.
全然できてない
私は スバルに
助けられてばっかりで―
You're the one who's always saving me.
I never could do anything for you.
何にもしてあげられなくて
And yet, you got yourself hurt,
and said it was for my sake...
それなのに スバルは
私のためだって傷ついて…
No, something had gotten into me back—
いや あん時は 俺がどうかして…
I was thinking only of myself.
自分のことばかりだった
I said it was all for you,
君のためって言いながら―
when I was really just drunk on
the idea of doing it for you.
君のために頑張る自分に
酔ってただけだ
I had it in my head that
if I said that, you'd accept it.
そうすれば 君はそれを
受け入れてくれると―
勝手に思ってた
Subaru...
スバル…
I'm sorry.
（スバル）ごめんな
I used you for my own self-satisfaction.
俺は君を利用して 悦に浸ってた
あの時の言葉は全部 正しかったよ
Everything you said back then was true.
I was wrong.
俺が間違ってた
But...
でも―
There's one thing I wasn't wrong about.
間違ってなかったこともある
君を助けたい　君の力になりたい
I want to save you.
I want to help you.
I honestly mean that.
それは本気で本当で ウソじゃない
It's no lie.
Yeah.
うん 分かってる
I know.
Why do you always save me?
どうして 私を助けてくれるの？
エミリアが好きだから
Because I love you.
俺は 君の力になりたいんだ
And I want to be your strength.
I'm a half-elf...
（エミリア）私 ハーフエルフ
I know that.
知ってるよ
I'm a silver-haired half-elf,
（エミリア）
銀色の髪で ハーフエルフで―
and many people hate me
because I look like the witch.
魔女と見た目が似てるからって
いろんな人から疎まれてるし―
They despise me...
嫌われてるの
ホントにすごーく嫌われてるの
They absolutely detest me!
見てた 知ってる
見る目のねえ奴らだよ
I saw. I know.
Those guys are all blind.
I don't have much experience with people,
人づきあいの経験が少ないから
友達とかいないの
so I don't have friends.
I'm naïve and lack common sense in a lot of ways,
so I say strange things sometimes.
非常識で世間知らずだから―
変なこと
言っちゃう時もあるし―
And the reason I want to be
the kingdom's ruler is really, really selfish.
王様になりたい理由だって
すごく すごーく自分勝手で…
No matter what anyone says about you,
エミリアが 誰に何て言われて―
no matter what you think of yourself,
自分で自分を
どう思っていようと―
I love you.
俺は君が好きだよ
大好きだ　超好きだ
I really love you! Like crazy!
I want to be with you all the time.
ずっと隣にいたい
ずっと手をつないでいたい
I want to hold your hand all the time.
If you name ten things you hate about yourself,
君が 自分の嫌いなところを
10個言うなら―
I'll list two thousand things I love about you.
俺は 君の好きなところを
2000個言う
That's the kind of
俺は 君をそうやって―
special treatment I want to give you.
俺の特別扱いしたいんだ
That's the first time I've received
special treatment that made me happy...
されて うれしい特別扱いなんて
生まれて初めて
Why two thousand?
どうして 2000個なの？
Because a hundredfold isn't enough
to express how I feel about you.
俺の気持ちを表現するのに
100倍じゃ 足りねえからだよ
うれしい
I'm happy...
I'm so happy.
本当にうれしい
誰かに 好きだなんて
言ってもらえる日がくるなんて―
I never even imagined I'd see the day
that someone told me they loved me.
考えたこともなかったから
What should I do?
私 どうしたらいいの？
You've told me so many of your feelings,
スバルが そうやって私に
気持ちを伝えてくれてるのに―
but I don't know what to do...
私 何をしたらいいのか
分からないの
You don't have to stress over it.
（スバル）
焦んなくていいよ
I'm not demanding an answer right away.
すぐに答えを
欲しがっちゃいないから
As far as I'm concerned, it's written in stone
that you'll give me an answer.
いずれ ちゃんとした形で―
しかも ＯＫもらうのは
俺の中で決定事項なんだし
And it'll be a positive one, at that.
Is it really all right?
いいの… かな
For me...
私が… 私なんかが―
For someone like me to be given
such happiness all the time?
こんなうれしいことばっかり
してもらって
To be so overjoyed...
こんなに幸せな気持ちで
ぜいたくな思いなんかして
I actually feel like it's indulgent.
Sure, it is. Go on and be indulgent.
いいじゃん しようよ ぜいたく
You can never have too much happiness.
幸せなんか いくらあったって
困りゃしないんだし―
If you have so much that it overflows,
you can always share it.
あふれかえって余ったら
配ったらいいしさ
You can take your time, Emilia.
ゆっくりでいいよ エミリア
You can take your time and slowly,
steadily fall in love with me.
ゆっくり じっくり―
のんびりと 俺を好きに
なってくれたらいい
As I walk by your side,
君の隣で歩きながら―
I'll do my best to make you
fall head over heels for me.
君をメロメロにできるように
頑張るから
Thank you, Subaru...
ありがとう スバル
Thank you
私を 助けてくれて
for saving me.
That's All This  StoryIs About
my time is spinning around
my
time
is
spin
ning
a
round
That's All This  StoryIs About
my
time
is
spin
ning
a
round
my time is spinning around
your
deep
black
eyes
your deep black eyes
I
for
got
what
time
it
is
I forgot what time it is
and
ou
r
me
mo
ries
are
gone…?
and our memories are gone…?
a
mai
ka
o
ri
ha
na
tsu
amai kaori hanatsu
the trap known as memories
tsu
i
o
ku
to
i
u
na
no
wa
na
tsuioku to iu na no wana
releases a sweet scent
sa
so
wa
re
to
ra
wa
re
sasoware toraware
it tempts and takes hold of me
na
ze
a
ra
ga
e
mo
se
zu
ma
ta
naze aragae mo sezu mata
and yet again, I’m somehow unable to resist
o
bo
re
te
shi
ma
u
no
oboreteshimau no
as I begin to drown in them
I
wish
you
were
here
I wish you were here
oh,
ne
ver
close
your
eyes
oh, never close your eyes
sear
ching
for
a
true
fate
searching for a true fate
do
ko
ka
ki
e
ta
a
no
nu
ku
mo
ri
wo
dokoka kieta ano nukumori wo
I keep searching for the warmth that disappeared off somewhere
o
i
ka
ke
tsu
zu
ke
te
mi
u
shi
nau
“Re:
Start”
oikaketsuzukete miushinau “Re:Start”
but after the last traces fade away, I "Re:Start"
so,
let
us
try
a
gain
so, let us try again
from
the
ve
ry
first
time
from the very first time
"It'll work out; I know it will" just like that, even now
"ki
t
to
ki
t
to"
so
u
ya
tte
i
ma
mo
"kitto kitto" sou yatte ima mo
da
re
mo
mi
na
e
n
ji
te
iru
daremo mina enjiteiru
each and every one of us is putting up a brave front
for
now,
I’ll
see
you
off
for now, I’ll see you off
and
we’ll
die
wai
ting
for
a
new
day
and we’ll die waiting for a new day
ni
do
to
nidoto
never again
and
we’ll
start
wai
ting
for
a
new
day
and we’ll start waiting for a new day
ki
mi
to…
kimi to…
together with you...